Chip Py Go-Go Collection 199
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1: Photographs, 2011-2020; 199chippy
  - Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band at Ibiza, 2011-04-02; 199chippy_0359; Chuck Brown play guitar and sings while performing with Chuck Brown Band. A photographer is visible behind him.
  - Bryan Mills play saxophone with Chuck Brown Band at Ibiza, 2011-04-02; 199chippy_0360; Bryan Mills play tenor saxophone while performing with Chuck Brown Band.
  - Mighty Moe plays congas with Chuck Brown Band at Ibiza, 2011-04-02; 199chippy_0361; Mighty Moe plays congas with Chuck Brown Band. Sweat drips from his face as he performs.
  - Chuck Brown and D. Floyd with Chuck Brown Band at Ibiza, 2011-04-02; 199chippy_0362; Chuck Brown turns to smile at the camera. He wears his guitar and holds a microphone in in right hand. Behind him D. Floyd faces the audience who watch him intensely.
  - D. Floyd performing with Chuck Brown Band at Ibiza, 2011-04-02; 199chippy_0363; D. Floyd performs with Chuck Brown Band. He holds a microphone in his right hand and points at the audience with his left hand.
  - Chuck Brown and KK performing with Chuck Brown Band at Ibiza, 2011-04-02; 199chippy_0364; From left to right Chuck Brown and KK sing together on stage. Chuck Brown is also playing guitar. Fans watches intently.
  - Christopher Lee at Ibiza, 2011-04-02; 199chippy_0365; Christopher Lee watches a performance on stage at Ibiza. His T-shirt reads 'the Godfather of Go Go'. Fans and Sweet Cherie are visible behind him.
  - Chuck Brown, KK, and Greg Boyer performing with Chuck Brown Band at Ibiza, 2011-04-02; 199chippy_0366; From left to right Chuck Brown plays the guitar, KK sings and holds a microphone in her right hand, and Greg Boyer plays trombone.
  - KK performing with Chuck Brown Band at Ibiza, 2011-04-02; 199chippy_0367; KK performs with Chuck Brown Band at Ibiza. She holds the microphone in her right hand and looks towards the audience.
  - D. Floyd performing with Chuck Brown Band at Ibiza, 2011-04-02; 199chippy_0368; D. Floyd performs with Chuck Brown Band. He holds a microphone in his right hand and points upward with his left hand.
  - Bryan Mills play saxophone with Chuck Brown Band at Ibiza, 2011-04-02; 199chippy_0369; Bryan Mills plays tenor saxophone while performing with Chuck Brown Band. A trumpet is visible to the right.
  - Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band at Ibiza, 2011-04-02; 199chippy_0370; Chuck Brown play guitar and sings while performing with Chuck Brown Band.
  - Greg Boyer playing trombone with Chuck Brown Band at Ibiza, 2011-04-02; 199chippy_0371; Greg Boyer plays trombone with Chuck Brown Band.
  - Chuck Brown playing electric guitar with Chuck Brown Band at Ibiza, 2011-04-02; 199chippy_0372; Chuck Brown play electric guitar while performing with Chuck Brown Band.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at Ibiza, 2011-04-06; 199chippy_0206; Sugar Rai performs with BE'LA DONA. She hold a microphone in her left hand and a tambourine in her right hand.
  - Miss Karis, Sugar Rai, and Sweet Cherie performing with BE'LA DONA at Ibiza, 2011-04-06; 199chippy_0207; From left to right Miss Karis, Sugar Rai, and Sweet Cherie perform with BE'LA DONA. Miss Karis and Sugar Rai both hold microphones in their left hands. Sweet Cherie plays the keys and sings into a microphone.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at Ibiza, 2011-04-06; 199chippy_0208; Sugar Rai performs with BE'LA DONA. She hold a microphone in her left hand and a tambourine in her right hand.
  - Miss Karris performing with BE'LA DONA at Ibiza, 2011-04-06; 199chippy_0209; Miss Karis performs with BE'LA DONA. She holds a microphone in her left hand.
  - Damila Adams performing with BE'LA DONA at Ibiza, 2011-04-06; 199chippy_0210; Damila Adams performs with BE'LA DONA. She holds a microphone in her hands.
  - Storm playing bass guitar with BE'LA DONA at Ibiza, 2011-04-06; 199chippy_0211; Storm plays bass guitar with BE'LA DONA.
  - Shannon Browne drumming with BE'LA DONA at Ibiza, 2011-04-06; 199chippy_0212; Shannon Browne plays drums during a performance with BE'LA DONA. Other performers are visible in the background.
  - Sweet Cherie, Damila Adams, Sugar Rai, and Storm performing with BE'LA DONA at Ibiza, 2011-04-06; 199chippy_0213; From left to right Sweet Cherie play the keys; Damila Adams and Sugar Rai sing; and Storm plays bass guitar while performing with BE'LA DONA.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at Ibiza, 2011-04-06; 199chippy_0214; Sugar Rai performs with BE'LA DONA. She hold a microphone in her right hand.
  - Sweet Cherie playing the keys with BE'LA DONA at Ibiza, 2011-04-06; 199chippy_0215; Sweet Cherie plays the keys while performing with BE'LA DONA.
  - Shorty Corleone and KeKe perform with Rare Essence at Club Rio, 2011-04-11; 199chippy_0707; KeKe and Shorty Corleone; sing into microphones during a performance with Rare Essence at Club Rio. Other band members are visible.
  - Go-Go Mickey on congas with Rare Essence at Club Rio, 2011-04-11; 199chippy_0708; Go-Go Mickey plays the congas during a performance with Rare Essence as Club Rio.
  - Go-Go Mickey on congas with Rare Essence at Club Rio, 2011-04-11; 199chippy_0709; Go-Go Mickey plays the congas during a performance with Rare Essence as Club Rio.
  - KeKe performing with Rare Essence at Club Rio, 2011-04-11; 199chippy_0710; KeKe sings into the microphone during a performance with Rare Essence at Club Rio. Other band members are visible.
  - D. Floyd performing at his All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0530; D. Floyd plays soprano saxophone at his All Star Birthday Bash.
  - Ms Kim performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0531; Ms Kim sings while performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash.
  - Ms Kim performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0532; Ms Kim sings while performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash.
  - Stomp Dogg performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0533; Stomp Dogg seated playing drums and cymbals at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash.
  - Stomp Dogg performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0534; Stomp Dogg seated playing drums and cymbals at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash.
  - Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0535; Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go with microphone wearing hat and sunglasses.
  - KeKe performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0536; KeKe sings into a microphone while performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center.
  - Ms Kim performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0537; Ms Kim sings into a microphone while performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center.
  - D. Floyd and a fan at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0538; D. Floyd sings into a microphone with his left hand and holds a cell phone in his right. A fan smiles and also holds the phone..
  - Steve Roy 'check the clock' at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0539; Steve Roy and the audience 'checks the clock' at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center.
  - D. Floyd performing on stage at his All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0540; D. Floyd performing on stage at his All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center.
  - Ms Kim and Steve Roy at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0541; Ms Kim and Steve Roy with microphone performing on stage.
  - KK and Ms Kim at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0542; From right to left KK and Ms Kim perform on stage with microphone.
  - Ms Kim and KK performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0543; Ms Kim (right) and KK (left) stand with their backs together during a performance at Marygolds Family Event Center for D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash. Ms Kim holds a microphone towards her mouth and smiles.
  - Go-Go Mickey performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0544; Go-Go Mickey plays the congas on stage at Marygolds Family Event Center for D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash.
  - Stomp Dogg performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0545; Stomp Dogg is wearing a pair of black headphones as he plays drums on stage at Marygolds Family Event Center for D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash. His drumsticks can be seen in the mid strike.
  - Stomp Dogg performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0546; Stomp Dogg is wearing a pair of black headphones as he plays drums on stage Marygolds Family Event Center for D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash. His drumsticks can be seen in the mid strike.
  - KeKe performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0547; KeKe singing on stage at Marygolds Family Event Center for D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash.
  - Stomp Dogg performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0548; Stomp Dogg is wearing a pair black headphones as he plays drums on stage at Marygolds Family Event Center for D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash. His drumsticks can be seen in the mid strike.
  - D. Floyd and a fan take over the stage at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0549; A fan dances at the front of the stage at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center. D. Floyd can be seen in the background singing.
  - D. Floyd and Miss Loretta Sims at his All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0550; D. Floyd poses with Miss Loretta Sims at his Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center.
  - Fan attending D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0551; A fan poses for a picture at Marygolds Family Event Center while attending D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash.
  - Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: The Godson of Go-Go, Steve Roy, and Ms Kim performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0552; Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go (left), Ms Kim (center), and Steve Roy (right), line the stage as they perform at Marygolds Family Event Center for D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash. Fans can be seen celebrating.
  - Stomp Dogg performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0553; Stomp Dogg is wearing a pair black headphones as he plays drums on stage at Marygolds Family Event Center for D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash.
  - Bojack on percussion at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0554; Bojack plays the cowbell on stage at Marygolds Family Event Center for D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash.
  - D. Floyd performing at his Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0555; D. Floyd is singing at Marygolds Family Event Center for his Birthday Bash event.
  - Sugar Bear performing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0556; Sugar Bear grips a microphone and points to the audience while singing at Marygolds Family Event Center for D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash.
  - Fan at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0557; A fan holds a cell phone in their left hand at Marygolds Family Event Center while attending D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash.
  - KeKe dancing at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0558; KeKe dances on stage at Marygolds Family Event Center while singing for D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash. She is likely dancing during a break in the music.
  - Ms Kim, KeKe, and a unknown person at D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-05-05; 199chippy_0559; KeKe (left) and Ms Kim (right) pose with an unidentified person (center) at Marygolds Family Event Center while performing D. Floyd's All Star Birthday Bash.
  - Shorty Corleone, KeKe, and D. Floyd perform with Rare Essence at Tradewinds, 2011-05-27; 199chippy_0711; Short Shorty Corleone, KeKe, and D. Floyd are all singing into their microphones. Other band members are visible.
  - KeKe performing with Rare Essence at Tradewinds, 2011-05-27; 199chippy_0712; KeKe sings into the microphone during a performance with Rare Essence at Rio. Other band members are visible.
  - Shorty Corleone interacting with fans while performing with Rare Essence at Tradewinds, 2011-05-27; 199chippy_0713; Short Shorty Corleone point his microphone towards the audience. Fans cheers and sings.
  - Shorty Corleone performing with Rare Essence at Tradewinds, 2011-05-27; 199chippy_0714; Shorty Corleone points his finger at the audience while performing with Rare Essence at Rio. Fans can be seen dancing.
  - Shorty Corleone interacting with fans while performing with Rare Essence at Tradewinds Night Club, 2011-05-27; 199chippy_0715; Shorty Corleone sings into this microphone while interacting with fans during a performing with Rare Essence at Tradewinds Night Club. Fans can be seen dancing.
  - KeKe; Shorty Corleone; Whiteboy; and D. Floyd performing as Rare Essence at Tradewinds, 2011-05-27; 199chippy_0716; Whiteboy, (left) KeKe (center left), Shorty Corleone (front center), and D. Floyd (right) performing as Rare Essence at Tradewinds. Other band members and fans are visible.
  - KeKe dancing during her performance with Rare Essence at Tradewinds, 2011-05-27; 199chippy_0717; KeKe bends at the knees and dances during her performance with Rare Essence at Tradewinds.
  - D. Floyd and Sugar Bear performing with Rare Essence at Tradewinds, 2011-05-27; 199chippy_0718; D. Floyd (right) looks over to Sugar Bear (left) who intensely looks out at the audience during their performance with Rare Essence at Tradewinds.
  - Sign at Tradewinds green room, 2011-05-27; 199chippy_0719; A sign notifies band members to only eat three chicken wings person.
  - KeKe celebrates a birthday at Tradewinds with Rare Essence, 2011-05-27; 199chippy_0720; KeKe holds tray of cupcakes to celebrate her birthday at Tradewinds. The cupcakes are decorated with shoes, handbags, lipsticks, microphones, and flowers. A banner across the from cupcakes reads 'Happy B Day Kee-Kee'.
  - Whiteboy performing with Rare Essence at Tradewinds, 2011-05-27; 199chippy_0721; Whiteboy sings with Rare Essence at Tradewinds. Fans and KeKe are visible in the background.
  - Whiteboy performing with Rare Essence at Tradewinds, 2011-05-27; 199chippy_0722; Whiteboy sings while playing guitar with Rare Essence at Tradewinds. He stands back to back with a fan. Fans and other band members are visible.
  - Whiteboy with a fan at Tradewinds, 2011-05-27; 199chippy_0723; Whiteboy poses for a photograph with a fan. His guitar strap is visible.
  - Rare Essence security detail at Tradewinds, 2011-05-27; 199chippy_0724; Two security details poses for a photograph during a Rare Essence show at Tradewinds.
  - Genny Jam performs with BE'LA DONA at Upscale Ballroom, 2011-05-30; 199chippy_0190; Genny Jam play electric guitar while performing with BE'LA DONA during a performance at Upscale Ballroom.
  - Sugar Rai and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA at Upscale Ballroom, 2011-05-30; 199chippy_0191; Sugar Rai and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA during a performance at Upscale Ballroom.
  - Miss Karis performs with BE'LA DONA at Upscale Ballroom, 2011-05-30; 199chippy_0192; Miss Karis performs with BE'LA DONA during a performance at Upscale Ballroom.
  - Sugar Rai and Too Smooth at Upscale Ballroom, 2011-05-30; 199chippy_0193; Sugar Rai and Too Smooth at a BE'LA DONA performance at Upscale Ballroom.
  - Genny Jam performs with BE'LA DONA at Upscale Ballroom, 2011-05-30; 199chippy_0194; Genny Jam plays an electric guitar with BE'LA DONA during a performance at Upscale Ballroom.
  - Shannon Browne performs with BE'LA DONA at Upscale Ballroom, 2011-05-30; 199chippy_0195; Shannon Browne plays drums with BE'LA DONA during a performance at Upscale Ballroom.
  - Miss Karis performs with BE'LA DONA at Upscale Ballroom, 2011-05-30; 199chippy_0196; Miss Karis performs with BE'LA DONA during a performance at Upscale Ballroom.
  - Miss Karis and Genny Jam perform with BE'LA DONA at Upscale Ballroom, 2011-05-30; 199chippy_0197; Miss Karis sings into a microphone and Genny Jam plays electric guitar while performing with BE'LA DONA during at Upscale Ballroom.
  - Genny Jam performs with BE'LA DONA at Upscale Ballroom, 2011-05-30; 199chippy_0198; Genny Jam plays an electric guitar with BE'LA DONA during a performance at Upscale Ballroom.
  - Sugar Rai, Genny Jam, and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA at Upscale Ballroom, 2011-05-30; 199chippy_0199; Sugar Rai plays tambourine, Genny Jam plays an electric guitar, and Miss Karis dances while performing with BE'LA DONA at Upscale Ballroom.
  - Sugar Rai and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA at Upscale Ballroom, 2011-05-30; 199chippy_0200; Sugar Rai plays tambourine and Miss Karis sings while performing with BE'LA DONA at Upscale Ballroom.
  - Sweet Cherie performs with BE'LA DONA at Upscale Ballroom, 2011-05-30; 199chippy_0201; Sweet Cherie play the keys with BE'LA DONA during a performance at Upscale Ballroom.
  - Shannon Browne drumming with BE'LA DONA at Upscale Ballroom, 2011-05-30; 199chippy_0202; Shannon Browne plays drums during a performance with BE'LA DONA. Other performers or fans are visible.
  - Sugar Rai and Too Smooth at the Upscale Ballroom, 2011-05-30; 199chippy_0203; Sugar Rai and Too Smooth pose at Upscale Ballroom.
  - Shannon Browne drumming with BE'LA DONA at Upscale Ballroom, 2011-05-30; 199chippy_0204; Shannon Browne plays drums during a performance with BE'LA DONA. Other performers or fans are visible.
  - DJ Dirty Rico with a fan at Upscale Ballroom, 2011-05-30; 199chippy_0205; DJ Dirty Rico slaps hands with a fan during a BE'LA DONA performance.
  - D. Floyd standing in front of the United States Capitol building at a statehood rally, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0373; D. Floyd at the statehood rally standing in front of United States Capitol building. The statehood rally included a teach-in with activists and musicians. It occurred on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol.
  - Chuck Brown standing in front of the United States Capitol building at a statehood rally, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0374; Chuck Brown at the statehood rally standing in front of United States Capitol building. The statehood rally included a teach-in with activists and musicians. It occurred on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol.
  - Chuck Brown performing on stage with Chuck Brown Band at the statehood rally in front of the United States Capitol, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0375; Chuck Bown performing with musicians on stage at the statehood rally in front of the United States Capitol building. The statehood rally included a teach-in with activist and musicians. It occurred on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol.
  - Chuck Brown performing on stage with Chuck Brown Band at the statehood rally in front of the United States Capitol building, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0376; Chuck Bown performing with musicians on stage at the statehood rally in front of the United States Capitol building. The statehood rally included a teach-in with activist and musicians. It occurred on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol.
  - Chuck Brown performing on stage with Chuck Brown Band at the statehood rally in front of the United States Capitol, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0377; Chuck Bown performing with musicians on stage at the statehood rally in front of the United States Capitol building. The statehood rally included a teach-in with activist and musicians. It occurred on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol.
  - Chuck Brown performing on stage with Chuck Brown Band at the statehood rally in front of the United States Capitol, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0378; Chuck Brown gestures with pointed finger while performing for 2011 D. C. Statehood rally at the United States Capitol.
  - Child watches Chuck Brown and Chuck Brown Band at statehood rally at the United States Capitol, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0379; Child sits on stage watching Chuck Brown perform during a D. C. Statehood rally at the United States Capitol.
  - Child reaches out to Chuck Brown during a statehood rally performance at the United States Capitol, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0380; Child reaches out to Chuck Brown with plastic miniature hanger during a D. C. Statehood rally performance at the United States Capitol.
  - Chuck Brown performs with Chuck Brown Band during a statehood rally at the United States Capitol, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0381; Chuck Brown plays electric guitar while performing with Chuck Brown Band during a D. C. Statehood rally at the United States Capitol.
  - KK and Chuck Brown perform with Chuck Brown Band during a statehood rally at the United States Capitol, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0382; KK and Chuck Brown perform together during a D. C. Statehood rally at the United States Capitol.
  - KK performs with Chuck Brown Band with Chuck Brown during a statehood rally at the United States Capitol, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0383; KK poses at a D. C. Statehood rally at the United States Capitol.
  - Child performs with Chuck Brown Band with Chuck Brown during a statehood rally at the United States Capitol, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0384; Child holds microphone and performs with Chuck Brown during a D. C. Statehood rally at the United States Capitol.
  - Peekaso paints while Chuck Brown and the Chuck Brown Band perform for statehood rally at the United States Capitol, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0385; Peekaso paints Chuck Brown and child performing during a D. C. Statehood rally at the United States Capitol.
  - KK and D. Floyd perform with Chuck Brown Band during a statehood rally at the United States Capitol, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0386; KK and D. Floyd perform with Chuck Brown Band during a D. C. Statehood rally at the United States Capitol.
  - KK performs with Chuck Brown Band at a statehood rally at the United States Capitol, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0387; KK performs with Chuck Brown Band during a D. C. Statehood rally at the United States Capitol.
  - Kwick Foot with Chuck Brown Band at a statehood rally at the United States Capitol, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0388; Kwick Foot gestures for camera during a D. C. Statehood rally performance with Chuck Brown at the United States Capitol.
  - Chuck Brown with Chuck Brown Band at a statehood rally at the United States Capitol, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0389; Chuck Brown reaches out with microphone to the audience while performing during a D. C. Statehood rally at the United States Capitol. The National Mall and Washington Monument are visible in the background.
  - KK, Cookie, and Chuck Brown sign autographs during statehood rally at the United States Capitol, 2011-06-09; 199chippy_0390; KK, Cookie, and Chuck Brown sign autographs during D. C. Statehood rally at the United States Capitol.